

SACHINDRA PRADHAN

Building 4173 Block 711 Road 1173, Tubli, Manama, Bahrain +97335037623 psachindra3@gmail.com 22nd of July 1995 in https://www.linkedin.com/in/sachindrapradhan-0a106917a

OBJECTIVE

Dynamic, Versatile and resourceful professional with valuable guest service and problem resolution expertize.

More than 2 years experience as Service crew member, cashier, Inventory incharge and as well as a Drive thru order taker. 2 years of experience as a Front office desk associate/supervisor is now looking to work in an environment that challenges me to continue learning from my peers, as well as to contribute my knowledge, enthusiasm and skill, data entry.

To learn every minute of things from my work and achieve goal by grabbing opportunities. I want to raise the position of my organisation and raise my carrer through climbing the ladder of success.

SKILLS

- Customer service.
- Typing.
- Handling telephone.
- Calendar and time management.
- Referral management.
- Flexible on shifts.
- Computer and Internet knowledge.
- Quick learner and Smart worker.
- Familiar with software like Ids and Micros.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Nationality-Indian Martial status- Single Father Name- Mr. Chandra kishore pradhan Mother Name-Mrs. Sangita pradhan

EXPERIENCE

16th July 2019 - Jasmis Corporation ,Bahrain Till date

Service crew/Cashier/Inventory

Service crew member a part of team handling guest and preparing food items.

- Duties upsold additional menu items beverages and desserts to increase restaurant profit.
- Duties accurately measured ingredients required for specific food items.
- Maintain sanitation, health and safety standard in all work areas.
- Perform general maintenance duties, including moping floors, washing dishes, wiping counters tops and emptying
- · Responsibilities conduct fast and good quality customer service and food in a timely manner.
- Assisted customers and prepare food, order counters and take orders in dine in and drive thru windows.
- Maintaining inventory levels and monthly inventory reports
- Record and labelling inventory items for future use.
- Always keep track of goods and supplies in the store.

12-02-2017 - 10- Mayfair hotels and resort, India 07-2019

Front office associate - Front office supervisor

- Checked guest in and out at the front desk of a busy hotel.
- Greeted guest and give them advice of the local area in regard to direction, activities and dinning.
- Resolve guest conflicts and complaints from the guests.
- · Assist the General manager in delegations of duties for office staff.
- Prepare log books for pass down information, lost and found items and new or unknown situation.
- Utilise computer program and Microsoft Office suite, primarily excel for filling and documentations.
- Inspect the property and rooms for safety or hygienic concerns.

5-05-2017 - 20- Mayfair hotels and resorts, India

11-2017 **Industrial Training**

> Undergone Industrial exposure training for 6 months in Food & Beverage production, Housekeeping, Front Office and F & B service Department.

28-02-2016 - 11- Convergys, Delhi India 07-2016

Call Centre Agent

- Answering approximately 200 inbound customer calls per day in a friendly and courteous manner.
- · Processing customers orders and sales providing receiving information.
- Prepare completeand accurate work including appropriately notating accounts as required.
- · The solid reputation of ensuring a highlighted level of guest satisfaction.

EDUCATION

INTERESTS

- · Listening to music.
- Volunteer work.
- Sports especially Soccer.
- Traveling

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi
- Nepali

Diploma in Hospitality Management

Α

2016 University of delhi

Bachelor degree in Political science

В

2014 Human potential Development centre

Computer Fundamentals, Ms office and Internet

Certificate course

Α

2013 St Roberts Higher Secondary School

Higher Secondary (Twelfth Grade)

В

ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS

Awarded 3 times best Employee of the month(quarterly) in jasmis corporation (Bahrain).

Employer of the month in the Department of Front office at Mayfair hotels and resort, India.

Certified from science fair for presenting a project on 'sustainable Development in the year 2012'

ACTIVITIES

Participated in Drama and Group songs in school.

Participated in different welfare activities.

Trekked.

Participated in cultural programme in independence day as Ncc cadet and school contigent.

Signature:
Sachindra

Pradhan